Guide to the Teamsters for a Democratic Union, New York - New Jersey Chapter Records WAG.136
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Legal, 1977-1994
  - Countryman v Shearson Lehman, Stein Roe et al., 1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Countryman v. Shearson et al. *87 C 3861 Briefs and Litigation, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Countryman v. Shearson et al. *87 C 3861, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Countryman v. Shearson et al. *87 C 3861, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - New York State Teamsters Health Fund v. Shearson Lehman;Briefs and Litigation, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - New York State Teamsters H&H Fund v. Shearson Lehman (87-C-718), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - New York State Teamsters H&H Fund v. Shearson Lehman (87-cv-718), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - New York State Teamsters H&H Fund v. Stein Roe Farnham et al ( 87-Civ-718); Memorandum of Defendant. re: Damages, June 29, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Countryman v. Shearson et al, Briefs and Litigation; Press, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Health Fund v. Stein (87-Civ-718), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Health Fund v. Stein (87-cv-718), 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.1); Interim Report, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.2); Interim Report, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.3); Interim Report, November 8, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.4,5,6); Interim Report, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.7); Interim Report, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.8,9,10); Interim Report, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 sec.11,12,13); Interim Report, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 Sec.8-13 and EBF 332; Pts 1+2: Corr.; Complaint; Lists, June 14, 1977-January 3, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 EBF 332 Pt 2); Interim Reports and Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 EBF.331); Interim Report, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 EBF.332 Pt 1); Interim Report; Correspondence, July 16, 1984-March 14, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 5138) Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733 EBF.317); Interim Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - U.S. v. IBT et al., La Cosa Nostra et al. (FBI #HQ 159-4733); Identity of Informant; Known as "ALPRO", undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - U.S v. Dellacroce et al. (CR-85 00178) Indictment, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - U.S v. Rastellt et al. (CR-85 00354) Indictment, June 11, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - U.S v. Salerno et al. (CR-85 00178) Indictment, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - U.S v. Salerno et al. (CR-86) Indictment; Press Release, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - U.S v. IBT: Overview of Govt. & Jackie Presser Investigation, May 9, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - U.S v. Salerno et al. (CR-85 0100) Indictment, June 13, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - U.S v. Salerno et al. (S 86 Cr, 245) Indictment, Notes of S. Jennik, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - U.S v. IBT; "Fat Tony" Salerno et al. (88 civ 4486) Complaint, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al.(88 Civ 4486) Summons, Memorandum of Law (Amicus); AUD in Opposition to Motion to Stay; Press Release; Outline of Complaint, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 Civ 4486) Declaration of Randy Mastro-RICO Suit, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 Civ 4486) Plaintiff's 1st Request for Admissions, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 Civ 4486): Exhibits A-I (AUD on Election Rules), undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 civ 4486) -Memorandum of Law in Support of Motion To Dismiss (for IBT), August 16, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 Civ 4486): Briefs and Litigation, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 civ 4486) - Briefs and Litigation; Affidavit - K.Paff; Motion to Intervene, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - RICO: Settlement U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 Civ 4486); Correspondence, Order 88 Civ 4486; Judge Edelstein's Explanation of ..., Resumes of Administrators, Press Releases, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (88 Civ 4486); Statements from AUD, IBT; Correspondence, 1987-1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - U.S v. IBT, et al. (90-8064): Notice of Motion for Leave to File as Amicus Curiae-AUD, August 10, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Candidates and Attorneys Manual (ACLU) Observers Manual, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Convention and Election Guides; Campaign Materials; Notes, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - U.S Area Conferences Revocation Hearing: Transcript of Proceedings (pp 670-899), May 27, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Area Conferences Revocation Hearing: Transcript of Proceedings (pp 900-1098 close of session), May 27, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Report of the Election Officer (Amy Gladstein), July 6, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Independent Review Board's Report on Investigation of Ron Carey, July 11, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Series VII: Resource Materials, 1977-1995
  Series VII consists of subject files related to the union and the industry, as well as generic materials on labor and the reform movement. Various rank-and-file groups are represented, including those in the Utility Workers, the CWA, (New Directions caucus) the UAW, postal employees, etc.
  - Company Resource Materials, 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Motor Carrier Annual Report, Carhaul Reports to the ICC; Ballot Instructions, 1977, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - UPS Forms 10-K, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Community Causes and Programs, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ESOP's (Employee Stock Ownership Program): Addenda re: Employee/ Profit Plans to Agreements with P.I.E Nationwide and Freight Systems, 1988; undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Government Materials (CDL), undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Deregulation: GAO Reports, Magazine Article, Notes of S. Jennik, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Health and Safety: Correspondence: Reports on Lung Cancer, OSHA; Agenda for Road Driver Workshop; M.V. Safety By Laws; Legal Text; Press, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Grand Central Terminal Health and Safety Coalition Newsletter (Local 808, IBT Participants), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - International Considerations, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Legal Texts re; LMRDA; Dues, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Public Employees: REF to Employee's Right to Appeal, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Puerto Rican Labor Tour (Correspondence, etc.), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - S & L Crisis: Corr. Lists of Endorsers; Cong. Persons Financial Democracy Campaign Literature, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Worker Resource CTR: Brochure, Testimony in support of.., Press, etc., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Association for Union Democracy: Position Papers; Bylaws $50 and Club News, Related Press, 1978-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A.U.D. Minutes of Meetings, 1983-1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Association for Union Democracy; Correspondence; Financial Reports, 1989-1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Newman v. CWA Local 1101: Flyers; Letter of Support, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mail Handlers Voice, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Postal Workers Union: 1986 Election; R&F Press, Campaign Materials (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Utility Workers Union LU. 1-2: Correspondence; R&F Press, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW); New Directions Movement Press; Interview w/Victor Reuther, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Press and Press Releases, 1980-1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Organized Crime Press, 1987-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings; Articles: Labor Movement (Organizing, etc.), undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Rank and File Newsletters - Other, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Material
  - Unprocessed Material (Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10)
- Series IX: Photographs, circa 1978-1987 (Box 11)
  Series IX includes photographs, contact sheets, and negatives from the late 1970s through late 1980s. These images are mainly from the Detroit area and depict TDU leaders and activists and demonstrations.